beallsflorida.com 2016-06-07

# Bealls Privacy Policy

### Types of Information We Collect

Information You Provide When You Interact with Bealls

We collect information, including personal information, from you in a variety of ways when you interact with Bealls through our Site. Examples of the types of information we may collect include your name, home address, email address, telephone number, mobile phone number, purchase and order information, and demographic information. You may provide such information, for instance, when:

  * You make an online purchase;
  * You create a personalized BeallsFlorida.com shopping account for your convenience;
  * You use our online order tracking;
  * You sign up to receive promotional emails or text messages (including offers and sales alerts);
  * You sign up to join a loyalty, rewards or similar program or club;
  * You provide your contact information and product preferences;
  * You participate in one of our promotional sweepstakes, contests and/or surveys or focus groups;
  * You use the Ratings & Reviews or related services and features; or
  * You submit a request to our Customer Service team.

Information Collected Automatically

In addition to information you provide directly, we may collect certain information using automated means such as cookies, web beacons, and web server logs. We may combine this automatically-collected information with other information we obtain about you, as described below. Examples of the types of information we may collect automatically include IP addresses, location information, mobile device identifiers, browser characteristics, and Site traffic and navigational information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file sent by a website that is stored on your hard drive by your computer's browser. This Site uses two kinds of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies exist only for as long as your browser remains open. We use session cookies, for example, to add items to your shopping bag. Persistent cookies last from visit to visit and do not go away when you exit your browser. We use persistent cookies to give you a more personalized shopping experience and to streamline your website navigation. For example, we use persistent cookies to show you items you have previously browsed on the Site.

Managing cookies varies from browser to browser, so please refer to your browser for further information. If you prefer, you usually can set your browser to remove or reject cookies. Please be aware that if you block cookies you may not be able to make purchases or use other interactive features on the Site.

Information from Other Sources

We may receive information about you from other sources and combine that information with information we collect about you through the Site. For instance, we obtain information from companies to enhance our existing customer information, such as improving the accuracy of the information we have about our customers. We are not responsible for the accuracy of the information provided by third parties, or how such third parties collect, use, or share such information.

### How We Use Your Information 

We may use information about you for various purposes, including:

  * Enhancing your online shopping experience with Bealls;
  * Processing purchases and other transactions;
  * Providing customer service, and following up on order questions and concerns;
  * Communicating with you about products, services, promotions, offers, and other news and information we think will be of interest to you;
  * Analyzing usage of, modifying, or improving the Site or other websites;
  * Contacting you regarding your use of the Site and, in our discretion, changes to our policies;
  * Preventing fraudulent activity and monitoring against threats; and
  * Carrying out any business function or other purpose as disclosed in this Policy or at the time you provide information to us.

### How We Share Your Information

Internally: We may share your information within Bealls, Inc., including with our affiliates.

Service Providers: We provide your information to companies that provide support services to Bealls, including, but not limited to, printers, marketing providers, analytics companies, web hosting providers, contest and survey administrators, call center service providers, payment processors, fulfillment and logistics vendors and data verification providers. We may also share your personal information with third parties that provide financial products and services related to our business, such as Bealls Charge. 

Legal or Safety Requirements: Bealls may disclose information about you in response to a legal order or request, or based upon our good faith belief that the disclosure is required or permitted by law. We also may disclose your information to protect users of our Site or the Site itself, to protect the public or to otherwise protect and defend the rights, property, security, safety of any party, or to protect our business interests.

Other Disclosures: We may disclose your information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any proposed or actual merger, purchase, sale, acquisition, or other transaction of all or any of our assets to another company. We also may share your information for any purpose listed elsewhere in this Policy, or as disclosed to you at the time the information was collected, or with your consent.

### Analytics and Online Tracking

We use third-party service providers such as Google Analytics, to assist us in better understanding how visitors use the Site. These providers place cookies on visitors' computers to collect information about how visitors navigate the Site, what products are browsed, and aggregate purchasing and other information. The information collected for this purpose is disclosed to, or directly collected by, these service providers. To learn more about opting out of data collection through Google Analytics, [click here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/181881?hl=en).

We and our third-party advertising vendors also use first- and third- party cookies to inform, optimize, and serve ads on the Site and other websites based upon a user's past visits to our Site and other websites, and to report upon how Bealls ad impressions and other ad services are related to the Site. We may combine and associate the information we collect through these technologies with other information we have collected from and about you. This combined information may be used by our third-party advertising vendors for interest-based advertising (also called "online behavioral advertising") on the Site and other websites across the internet in order to personalize your online experience, improve our Site and other websites, and to tailor Bealls and other companies' marketing to you. To learn more about this process or to opt out of this type of advertising, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

Note that your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit a "Do Not Track" signal to websites and online services you visit. There is no consensus among industry participants as to what "Do Not Track" means in this context. Like many websites and online services, this Site is not designed to respond to "Do Not Track" signals received from browsers. To find out more about "Do Not Track," you may wish to visit [ http://www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

### Children Under 13

The Site is not intended for children, and we do not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have received such information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete the information.

### Email

To stop receiving advertising emails from Bealls, you may click the unsubscribe button in an email that you receive from us.

### Security

Bealls uses appropriate safeguards to help protect the information you provide to Bealls online. Although Bealls uses reasonable efforts to secure information, transmission via the Internet is not completely secure and we cannot guarantee the security of information collected through the Site. If you cannot access the secure server, you may place your order by telephone at 800.569.9038, Monday-Saturday 9-9 or Sunday 10-8 EST.

### California Privacy Rights

California law permits customers in California to request a notice from us providing certain information about what personal information we share with third parties for direct marketing purposes. Each customer may make one request per year by submitting the request in writing to:

  * Bealls Department Stores
  * Attention: Customer Care-California Privacy Rights
  * P.O. Box 25207
  * Bradenton, FL 34206-5207

### Contact Information

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may click here to contact us. Our mailing address is:

  * Bealls Department Stores
  * Attention: Customer Care
  * P.O. Box 25207
  * Bradenton, FL 34206-5207

### Updates to this Policy

As we continue to offer new and different types of content and services, Bealls may modify this Policy. Should there be a material change to our information practices, it will be applied on a go-forward basis, and we will notify you by updating the date at the beginning of this Policy. Bealls encourages you to review this Policy each time you visit this Site.
